<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>One Fact</title>
    <link>https://onefact.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on One Fact</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://onefact.org/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://onefact.org/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://onefact.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building the first public dataset of group homes in the US</title>
      <link>https://onefact.org/assisted-living/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onefact.org/assisted-living/</guid>
      <description>This research project started as a result of spending hundreds of hours on the phone trying to find a home for someone suffering from severe schizophrenia and no income or insurance, and realizing how difficult it was to get a simple list of where Medicaid would pay for their housing.
This fact &amp;ndash; that we couldn&amp;rsquo;t access a comprehensive list of group homes or assisted living facilities for someone in need &amp;ndash; made us realize that we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t gaslight ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Involved</title>
      <link>https://onefact.org/get-involved/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onefact.org/get-involved/</guid>
      <description>Checklist for application: Assisted Living Map  Watch the talk we presented at the Machine Learning for Public Health workshop Read the paper we published describing the open dataset. Familiarize yourself with the codebase for the open dataset Submit a pull request to the repo with an example of an analysis you have done of all 44,000+ assisted living facilities in the United States (could be descriptive statistics, a plot, a model, a map, etc - you choose :) Send us an email (hello@onefact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Summer of Code Ideas List</title>
      <link>https://onefact.org/ideas-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onefact.org/ideas-list/</guid>
      <description>This is a sampling of the ideas available for potential GSoC 2022 contributors - feel free to propose your own! The goal is to start from a basic fact about the world, and use data analysis, infrastructure, and open source software to make that fact accessible to the public, researchers, and policymakers, to help them create systematic change and improve health through better policy and decision-making.
A sampling of our mentors&amp;rsquo; past open source work:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>University of Maryland</title>
      <link>https://onefact.org/talks/umd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://onefact.org/talks/umd/</guid>
      <description>Fallback text here for unsupporting browsers, of which there are scant few.  --</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
